

Stu Coston

385-288-0899 stu.coston@gmail.com www.stucoston.com

Profile

For the last 7 years I've worked as a project manager on \$2.3B worth of Government programs and a number of large scale construction projects. During this time, I fell in love with website design, graphic design, content marketing, and digital marketing. I have been building brands, designing digital experiences for businesses and start-ups for 5 years. A designer at heart, my passion is catching consumer attention and creating experiences that entice users to take action.

Skills

HTML5/CSS3/JS

••••••

SEO

••••••

Asana / Slack / GitHub

••••••

Visual Storytelling

••••••

Email Marketing

Adobe Creative Cloud

Work History

Program and Contracts Manager 2012-2017

United States Air Force

Creative Designer
2014-Present
Goby Creative

Assistant Project Manager 2018-Present
CDI Contractors

Education

United States Air Force Academy 2008-2012
Bachelor of Science
Systems Engineering / Business

Experience

Leader

Managed 4 person marketing team for local political candidate; established brand identity, coordinated email marketing (mailchimp), scheduled social media posts, managed social media advertising, designed website and landing pages, and directed video productions -- came in 2nd with 80% less funding than other 4 candidates

Co-Founded Digital Marketing Agency-- established business operations standards; worked with clients to define requirements, establish and meet marketing goals, create digital marketing campaigns, and design websites

Led 9-person cross-functional team to on-time award of \$450M production contract -- created budget, established milestones, and identified project scope requirements

Launched an online dropshipping T-shirt brand -- utilized an exclusive ambassador program to jump start brand awareness

Designer

Designed websites and graphics for bands, personal trainers, small businesses, churches, political candidates, and local organizations -- decreased average page load time by 40%, got several clients to the first page on Google

Created style guide for corporate external marketing across multiple mediums -- https://styleguide.gobycreative.com/

Communicator

Prepared a 4 year forecast for a \$1.3B pilot training system -- built relationships with vendors and end users to understand requirements and secured funding from leadership

Managed \$2B/2000 person contract transition -- established weekly and quarterly status reports to stakeholders to solidify integritous relationships and deliver quality results

Worked 100% remotely on a 4 person marketing team for 2 years -- created eCommerce websites, custom coded websites, WordPress websites, and custom graphics for clients